FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
JUST GIVE UP
SADAKO'S
BLACK MAGIC
I'm so happy! The herbs
we dried came out awesome.
- Hey, does anyone wanna try a little?
- You should make yourself a drink first.
How 'bout... make Joe drink some later?
Good idea!
The blackout curtains for the café are
all reserved. We'll pick them up from
audiovisual the day before. And the wall
paintings and hallway fliers will somehow
get done on time. Good.
Woah! We are way behind schedule!
I mean, yeah.
That's not good. I mean like we might
not make it if we're only working on it
- during school hours.
- Maybe...
Hey, Sadako still hasn't come back yet.
It's fine! Don't worry!
- We just saw her earlier.
- Yeah, we did. She wasn't feeling the
best, but she said it's not a big problem
or anything.
Uh-huh!
- Oh, what are the names of those herbs?
- Fish mint and Japanese geranium.
- That one's good for digestion, right?
- Chizu, wanna try it?
Yeah, sure!
Andy, take care of this one too.
Alrighty.
Wow.
Oh, hey Ryu!
Sorry! Wish I could help.
- You got practice, it's all good.
- Summer prelims happen right
after the festival's over, huh?
Hey guys, what're we gonna
with the bottom part over here?
Where?
- Here. Were we gonna add some wires?
- Huh... I dunno, we gotta ask Kazehaya.
- Where the hell is he anyway?
- It's rare for him to slack off like this.
Shota!
, Ryu. Oh, right. I bet everyone's
getting to work already. My bad.
Yeah, when I stopped by, they seemed
like they had something to ask you.
I see.
Did you tell her the truth?
Yeah. Got turned down.
I guess I was troubling her.
She didn't seem to want people to
misunderstand our relationship.
Kuronuma thinks that everything I've
done for her... was just me protecting her
feelings... and that's all.
So, I told her... laid it out on
the table... It wasn't enough.
But I couldn't hold it in any longer.
Uh... man.
You know... it hurts more than I thought.
I didn't realize I was causing so
much anxiety... that it even made her cry.
That freakin' wench!
You look awful.
Oh Kurumi.
What do you mean friends?
I think you mean rivals.
I was... rejected by Kazehaya after all.
And your point?
Do you seriously think we're in the same
position? 'Cause that's a huge insult. You
don't deserve to be called my rival.
- Huuuuh?!
- Ugh! You are so annoying! Let go!
Is it... because I was... rejected?
- It's because you didn't put up a fight.
- Huh?
And 'cause whatever you did hurt Kazehaya.
Hurt him? How did I...?
Is it... because he still worries
about me when he has someone he likes?
- 'Cause I was so much troubl--
- It's because you're dense!
Kazehaya was the one who never felt
sorry for you. In fact, he was the only
one, wasn't he? Even in the beginning of
first year Chizu and Ayane started talking
to you because they pitied you!
Tell me. When you look at
him, what do you even see?!
What do I...
Don't even dare think
that I'm the same as you!
I made sure to lay it all out.
... See?
I got rejected...
but I clearly told him my
feelings. I'm nothing like you!
But... wasn't I was always looking at
Kazehaya? In fact, I couldn't stop my eyes
from following him wherever he went.
My goodness, that sure was tasty!
Sawako's curry is always the most
- delicious.
- Hashed beef rice
Hashed beef...
WE'RE ALL GATHERING AT MY HOUSE
TO WORK ON THE COSTUMES.
SAWA, YOU COME OVER TOO
IF YOU CAN!
I- Is it okay if I go out?
Right now? Just to Chizu's house.
I-Isn't it kinda late?
For school festival prep?
Yes, for the costume march.
Costume?!
Ah. I got some Karinto as a gift,
so you should take them with you.
Uh, Karinto?
- Be careful on your way there.
- Ah, right! Yes. Be careful!!
Uh-huh!
I'm heading out!
The school festival, huh... I remember when
I was in high school, I was in charge of
making the floats too.
Oh yeah. Well, I helped out
with the food stand situation.
Strawberry and
chocolate. Vanilla and cherry...
- Drink floats?
- And you know cutting a
strawberry with a saw is really hard!
I love you... but I don't know
what we're talking about anymore...
Don't get caught.
Slowly now, slowly.
- It's stuck, it won't budge!
- Lift it, come on!
What do you guys think you're doing? Huh?
I thought bringing the floats outside of
campus was prohibited, wasn't it?
Aw help us out come on! Just pretend
you didn't see us, please, we need this!
We can't finish it in time otherwise.
- Pin, it's your class!
- Well, to be honest I kinda don't care.
Uh... you don't care?
- Even if it's your class?
- Do it. Just don't get caught by the
other teachers, you brats. Or it'll be a
pain in the butt.
- Well we're off the hook, but now what?
- First, lift up that side.
Will do.
Shota! -Whoa! -Hey! Listen! I know you're
an angsty teenager or whatever now, but
when did you become such
a big, stupid jerk? -Huh?
"Huh?" My ass... Acting interested just to
lead her on? How scummy can you be? Even
though you look so innocent.
Poor Kuronuma. You dumped her?
- You've got it backwards!
- You had me completely fooled. Never, in a
million years would I think you'd be that
eager to reject a chick!
So, then... Tell me. What do you
think you'll be when you grow up?
- Gonna be a host? A gigolo? Or maybe...
- She turned me down!
- Huh?
- You heard me!
Wha-? But in the cafeteria, didn't
you dash off to go and reject her?
Why would I?!
- Is that-...? Kazehaya?
- Ah, Pin already got ahold of you?
- My bad! You guys go on without me!
- Okay!
Okay!
- Kazehaya's always got it tough!
- You should go save him then.
- Hold the other side.
- I went to confess to her.
Although it didn't go well.
I was rejected.
Hmm... I get it.
So you flubbed it! You were only able to
squeeze out a few sad words like a booger,
huh? I can't believe it,
you're such a dumbass!
You're wrong! I said what I needed to!
It's already over. Buzz off.
Yeah, you're right. Anyway I think you
said something about not understanding
Kuronuma but, you always get so
overwhelmed by your own stuff y'know?
So forget about it. Who
cares? You should just give up.
But why? This makes no
sense. It doesn't match up.
Huh? I wonder why.
Oh, that... I think it goes like... this.
I butted in without asking!
Oh, I see it now!
Yeah, that's better.
Thank you, Sadako!
I'm gonna go and get us some drinks.
Uh, Chizu.
What's up?
It's, uh... uh... I want
to thank you for today.
For texting me and
inviting me over to your house.
And also... for what you said.
When we've been here for you too. How much
longer are you gonna be okay with putting
- yourself down?
- So I'm grateful for that.
It's just... last year when I started
getting closer with you and Ayane...
That was the the- first time in my
whole entire life... I was actually liked by
someone.
- Wai...
- I... I said it.
Yup. So. Don't you forget that!
Now, let's get those drinks!
Aren't you glad? What you just
said made Chizu super happy!
What I said?
With only words?
I made sure to lay it all out.
...But I clearly told him my feelings.
Have I really... said everything?
Have I made it clear to Kazehaya?
K... Kurumi. Good morn...
Sh... She's disappointed in me.
- Sadako!
- Master!
I-I think I maybe, kinda, showed you
something very extra embarrassing
yesterday...
Not at all! Actually I...
Hold it. -You've really gone
and done it this time. -Uh...
What do you want with
her? Stay away! Scram!
Oh wow, so mean!
I told you not to do anything
uncalled-for! Do you have any idea what
- you've done?!
- Oh, uh, wait did I do
that?! I'm sorry, Sadako!
So yeah, about Kazehaya I think
that he might like you after all!
What?!
Why're you saying that
in front of everyone?!
N- No You've got it wrong!
It's a misunderstanding!
It's not that kind of "like."
Woah. What's going on here?
Uh I dunno, but I guess Sadako's
denying her relationship with Kazehaya.
What the heck?
- Ka--
- Kazehaya, Ryu, you guys are late!
Yeah, everyone's already
together... uh-wha-? Why's it so crowded?
- Uhh... Kazeha--
- No you don't!
No you don't!
- Come here!
- Huh? But isn't this really bad?!
- Just shut your damn mouth!
- You guys see that? So, what is up?
It's fine.
Everything's just fine
- Can we finish the float in time?
- We'll figure it out.
- I dunno about that.
- Probably gonna need
an all-nighter before.
Yeah. Wait, not again...
What was that? See?
it's probably just a rumor.
- He didn't even say anything to her.
- I knew it.
I know I'm not one to talk, but you
might be a little too quiet, I think.
If... things continue like this... I wonder
if Kazehaya's going to stop talking to me
altogether...
Am I just going to stare at his back
forever... Never able to even utter a "Good
morning,"?
It's possible he may
never smile at me ever again.
He may even avoid me.
I remember, when Kazehaya
was waiting here for me.
He was the one who came to talk to me.
Did I do something bad... maybe?
Why are we still having this conversation?
You're right.
Having trouble controlling that mouth
of yours? Want me to sew it up for ya?!
- Oh, this isn't good...
- Yeah well, you know,
I'm straightforward, so...
And I really don't give a crap, kay?!
Move it, you're both in my way.
Do you mind doing that
stuff somewhere else?
Oh right. Did something
happen after we chatted?
Huh? After what?
When you asked about the stuff with
Sadako and Kazehaya. Y'know the drama?
- What'chu say?!
Wait a sec, Kurumi! Don't tell me,
you're plotting something scummy again?!
You better not have
done anything to Sawako!
Done something? Well, I told her off
of course. If that's what you mean.
You what?!
She was too much of a coward to give
him her Valentine's chocolates. I wasn't
- wrong.
- What? How do you know about that?
So, this entire damn
thing was because of you!
Uh-huh! So I did get in her way! But why
does any of that matter? Huh?! Sawako's
the one who decided not to give them
to him! I didn't stop her! I am not the
problem!
- Ohhh. Good point.
- No, interfering is still wrong.
Wai- You mean... You had a
crush on Kazehaya too, Kurumi?!
Use your inside voice.
That's right.
Really now... This is a
problem isn't it... Ah!
Then if I were to go out with Sadako...
it'd be a good thing for you, right?
Stay out of her business!
Wait, so you're not trying to stop her?
No, I'm not... but I refuse to believe I
lost to such a pathetic girl. She's a lot
of things, but I didn't
think spineless was one of them!
- It's pathetic!
- Wait...
Kurumi!
So it's true I
guess... Kazehaya does like Sadako...
It's none of your business, Kento.
Why not? I mean, I can't leave things this
way. This is totally for Sadako, ya know.
It's for Sawako? You mean for you!
This is all about you trying to prove
you're a "nice guy". You know all that
"charity" you've done out of the
"goodness of your heart"? It's causing her
an extraordinary amount of pain.
See how messy it is when
outsiders butt in. Do you get that now?
Leave them alone.
LITERATURE HISTORY SOCIAL SCIENCE
MATHEMATICS NATURAL SCIENCE
WONDERFUL TABLE SETTINGS
INTRODUCTION TO HERBAL TEA
This whole time... I never
really looked at him.]
And I was never the one...
who put in the effort.
I want to tell you Right now. For real.
Next time: "Reach..."